export let easyQuestionList = [
  {
    question: "What famous Irish band was phil Lynott in?",
    answer: "Thin lizzy",
    potentialAnswer: ["Def Leopard", "The Dubliners", "U2", "The Pogues", "The Beatles"],
  },
  {
    question: "What famous Guitar Brand Did Rory Gallagher Use?",
    answer: "Fender",
    potentialAnswer: ["Gibson", "Ibanez", "Harley Benton", "PRS", "Schecter", "Gretsch"],
  },
  {
    question: "Which legendary British rock band released the album 'Dark Side of the Moon?",
    answer: "Pink Floyd",
    potentialAnswer: ["Led Zeppelin", "The Rolling Stones", "The Beatles", "Black Sabbath", "Queen"],
  },
  {
    question: "Who is the lead guitarist of the band Guns N' Roses?",
    answer: "Slash",
    potentialAnswer: ["Jimmy Page", "Eddie Van Halen", "Kirk Hammett", "Dave Mustaine", "Angus Young"],
  },
  {
    question: "What American band released the albums 'Master of Puppets' and 'Metallica?",
    answer: "Metallica",
    potentialAnswer: ["Megadeth", "Slayer", "Anthrax", "Pantera", "Iron Maiden"],
  },
  {
    question: "Which band is known for the hit song 'Sweet Child o' Mine?",
    answer: "Guns N' Roses",
    potentialAnswer: ["Aerosmith", "Bon Jovi", "Queen", "Journey", "Def Leppard"],
  },
  {
    question: "Which band is known for the song 'Hotel California?",
    answer: "Eagles",
    potentialAnswer: ["Fleetwood Mac", "The Doors", "The Beach Boys", "The Byrds", "Creedence Clearwater Revival"],
  },
  {
    question: "Which member of The Beatles was known as the 'Quiet Beatle?",
    answer: "George Harrison",
    potentialAnswer: ["John Lennon", "Paul McCartney", "Ringo Starr", "Pete Best", "Stuart Sutcliffe"],
  },
  {
    question: "What band is known for the song 'Dream On'?",
    answer: "Aerosmith",
    potentialAnswer: ["Guns N' Roses", "Queen", "Journey", "Bon Jovi", "Foreigner"],
  },
  {
    question: "Which band is famous for the song 'Imagine'?",
    answer: "John Lennon",
    potentialAnswer: ["The Beatles", "George Harrison", "Paul McCartney", "Elton John", "David Bowie"],
  },
  {
    question: "Which rock band is known for the hit song 'Livin' on a Prayer'?",
    answer: "Bon Jovi",
    potentialAnswer: ["Aerosmith", "Def Leppard", "Journey", "Poison", "Motley Crue"],
  },
  {
    question: "Who is the drummer for The Beatles?",
    answer: "Ringo Starr",
    potentialAnswer: ["John Bonham", "Keith Moon", "Charlie Watts", "Neil Peart", "Lars Ulrich"],
  },
  {
    question: "What band is known for the song 'Another One Bites the Dust'?",
    answer: "Queen",
    potentialAnswer: ["The Rolling Stones", "Led Zeppelin", "AC/DC", "Aerosmith", "Bon Jovi"],
  }
];



export let normalQuestionList = [
  {
    question: "Who was the original lead singer of the band AC/DC?",
    answer: "Bon Scott",
    potentialAnswer: ["Brian Johnson", "Phil Rudd", "Cliff Williams", "Angus Young", "Malcolm Young"],
  },
  {
    question: "Which American rock band released the album 'Appetite for Destruction?",
    answer: "Guns N Roses",
    potentialAnswer: ["Motley Crue", "Aerosmith", "Van Halen", "Def Leppard", "Bon Jovi"],
  },
  {
    question: "Which band is known for the song 'Stairway to Heaven?",
    answer: "Led Zeppelin",
    potentialAnswer: ["Black Sabbath", "Deep Purple", "Queen", "Pink Floyd", "The Who"],
  },
  {
    question: "Who was the frontman of the band Queen?",
    answer: "Freddie Mercury",
    potentialAnswer: ["David Bowie", "Mick Jagger", "Robert Plant", "Steven Tyler", "Axl Rose"],
  },
  {
    question: "Which rock band is known for the hit song 'Don't Stop Believin?",
    answer: "Journey",
    potentialAnswer: ["Foreigner", "REO Speedwagon", "Styx", "Kansas", "Boston"],
  },
  {
    question: "Who is the lead singer of Pearl Jam?",
    answer: "Eddie Vedder",
    potentialAnswer: ["Chris Cornell", "Kurt Cobain", "Scott Weiland", "Layne Staley", "Dave Grohl"],
  },
  {
    question: "Which band released the song 'Enter Sandman'?",
    answer: "Metallica",
    potentialAnswer: ["Megadeth", "Slayer", "Pantera", "Anthrax", "Iron Maiden"],
  },
  {
    question: "Who is the guitarist for Led Zeppelin?",
    answer: "Jimmy Page",
    potentialAnswer: ["Eric Clapton", "Jeff Beck", "Jimi Hendrix", "David Gilmour", "Pete Townshend"],
  },
  {
    question: "Which band is known for the album 'Back in Black'?",
    answer: "AC/DC",
    potentialAnswer: ["Aerosmith", "Van Halen", "Guns N' Roses", "Kiss", "Def Leppard"],
  },
  {
    question: "Which band had a hit with the song 'Every Breath You Take'?",
    answer: "The Police",
    potentialAnswer: ["U2", "Genesis", "Dire Straits", "Simple Minds", "INXS"],
  }
];



export let hardQuestionList = [
  {
    question: "Which rock band had hits like 'Smells Like Teen Spirit' and 'Come As You Are?",
    answer: "Nirvana",
    potentialAnswer: ["Pearl Jam", "Soundgarden", "Alice in Chains", "Foo Fighters", "Red Hot Chili Peppers"],
  },
  {
    question: "Who was the drummer for the band The Who?",
    answer: "Keith Moon",
    potentialAnswer: ["John Bonham", "Ringo Starr", "Charlie Watts", "Neil Peart", "Travis Barker"],
  },
  {
    question: "Which American rock band released the album 'Californication?",
    answer: "Red Hot Chili Peppers",
    potentialAnswer: ["Pearl Jam", "Foo Fighters", "Nirvana", "Soundgarden", "Alice in Chains"],
  },
  {
    question: "Which album by The Beatles is often considered one of the greatest of all time and features songs like 'A Day in the Life' and 'Lucy in the Sky with Diamonds?",
    answer: "Sgt. Peppers Lonely Hearts Club Band",
    potentialAnswer: ["Abbey Road", "Revolver", "The White Album", "Rubber Soul", "Let It Be"],
  },
  {
    question: "Which band's drummer was John Bonham?",
    answer: "Led Zeppelin",
    potentialAnswer: ["The Who", "Cream", "The Beatles", "The Rolling Stones", "Pink Floyd"],
  },
  {
    question: "Which band released the song 'Bohemian Rhapsody?",
    answer: "Queen",
    potentialAnswer: ["The Beatles", "Led Zeppelin", "Pink Floyd", "The Rolling Stones", "David Bowie"],
  },
  {
    question: "Who is known as the 'Godfather of Heavy Metal?",
    answer: "Ozzy Osbourne",
    potentialAnswer: ["Tony Iommi", "Lemmy Kilmister", "Rob Halford", "James Hetfield", "Kirk Hammett"],
  },
  {
    question: "Who is regarded as the most unique guitarist(Impossible)?",
    answer: "Jeff Beck",
    potentialAnswer: ["Prince", "Alan Holdsworth", "Nigel Tufnel", "Les Paul" ],
  },
  {
    question: "Which band released the album 'OK Computer'?",
    answer: "Radiohead",
    potentialAnswer: ["Nirvana", "Pearl Jam", "Blur", "Oasis", "The Smashing Pumpkins"],
  },
  {
    question: "Who is the lead singer of the band Soundgarden?",
    answer: "Chris Cornell",
    potentialAnswer: ["Eddie Vedder", "Kurt Cobain", "Layne Staley", "Scott Weiland", "Dave Grohl"],
  },
  {
    question: "Which band released the song 'Black Hole Sun'?",
    answer: "Soundgarden",
    potentialAnswer: ["Pearl Jam", "Nirvana", "Alice in Chains", "Foo Fighters", "Red Hot Chili Peppers"],
  },
  {
    question: "Who played bass guitar for the band The Clash?",
    answer: "Paul Simonon",
    potentialAnswer: ["Sid Vicious", "John Entwistle", "John Paul Jones", "Flea", "Duff McKagan"],
  }
];

